ilovelindsay.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Lindsay

Bell-Carter Foods, Inc. respects the privacy interests of our web site visitors. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information that we collect, the uses we make of that information, and how you can correct or request deletion of any personal identifying information you choose to give us.

### Information We Collect

In general, Bell-Carter Foods, Inc. does not collect personal identifying information from visitors to this web site unless such information is provided by the individual. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of Bell-Carter Foods, Inc.'s Internet servers, including the type of operating system and browser being used by the visitor. The information we collect allows us to make statistical analyses of the use of our site, to improve the content of our site, and to customize our site to better suit your needs.

### Use Of Your Information

We may use aggregated information, which does not identify you personally, for advertising, marketing, promotional and other business purposes. Should you choose to provide personal identifying information, we may use and disclose that information in a number of ways related to your use of our site. We may use your personal identifying information in connection with sending you specific, targeted information that may be of interest to you. We may use your contact information, such as your e-mail address, to acknowledge your request for information or for other similar purposes. We will not sell our member contact list or provide your personal identifying information to any other person or entity in the ordinary course of our business, although we reserve the right to transfer such information in connection with a change in ownership of Bell-Carter Foods, Inc. or its assets.

### Cookies

We make use of "cookies," which are small sets of information stored onto your computer in connection with your use of our web site. We may use information gathered by cookies to measure certain traffic patterns on our web site or for similar purposes. A user does not need to have the cookie function of their browser turned on in order to use this web site. If you arrived at our site through a link from another site, it is also possible that these other sites may place a cookie or other identifier on your computer. We do not control and are not responsible for the use of cookies or other identifiers by anyone except Bell-Carter Foods, Inc..

### Corrections and Deletions

If you want to see the personal information we have collected about you from this site, or if you believe any information we have is incorrect and you wish to correct it, please write to us at the address given at the end of this Privacy Policy. If we change or delete information in response to your request, we will discontinue using it; however, some information may remain in backup records and may take time to be ultimately purged.

### Security

While we take reasonable steps to protect your personal identifying information. Given the nature of the Internet, we cannot ensure complete security and we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of any person or entity other than Bell-Carter Foods, Inc. Although we take precautions against security breaches, hackers pose a threat to any Internet user, and the legal and regulatory status of matters on the Internet are uncertain both in the United States and abroad. For these reasons, we cannot guarantee that all of your personal identifying information will never be disclosed in ways you do not expect or which are not described in this Privacy Policy. We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, we obey court orders, and we honor subpoenas and other legal process. Your personal identifying information may be disclosed if we are compelled by law or legal process to disclose it. We may also disclose such information if we determine, in our sole discretion, that disclosure would be useful in connection with investigating possible noncompliance either with the law or with any policy of Bell-Carter Foods, Inc.

### Consent

Anyone under 18 should not send any information about themselves to us, including information like your name, address or e-mail address. Bell-Carter Foods, Inc. does not knowingly collect personally identifying information from anyone under the age of 18. In the event that we learn that we have collected such information from an individual under 18 without parental consent, the information will be deleted from our database as soon as reasonably possible.

Bell-Carter Foods, Inc. reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. Questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [policy@bellcarter.com](mailto:policy@bellcarter.com).
